<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Lokesh-Devops</title>
    <link>https://lokeshjawane.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Lokesh-Devops</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lokeshjawane.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automate SAM with CICD</title>
      <link>https://lokeshjawane.github.io/posts/sam-cicd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lokeshjawane.github.io/posts/sam-cicd/</guid>
      <description>Lambda deployment pipeline This is the part2 of SAM(part1)), In the first part we have implemented SAM to ease the lambda deployment. But to make it more easier, lets now automate it using CICD practice. The aim is to have a simplified process for developer to automated the lambda deployment process even their devops is offline :D.
In this post, we will further automated the the lambda deployment with CICD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAM for serverless lamda</title>
      <link>https://lokeshjawane.github.io/posts/sam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lokeshjawane.github.io/posts/sam/</guid>
      <description>Lambda Using SAM It been a long time i have worked on lambda deployment and most of the time doing it manually just because of on-demand request for the deployment. But then thought to remove the dependency from me and have some event based automation in place and can be easily adopt by developer.
But as there are many lambda&amp;rsquo;s in project which uses diff technologies, the challenge was to manage the automation for each and manage the package to build the code and i came across one thing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure AWS Env</title>
      <link>https://lokeshjawane.github.io/posts/aws-account-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lokeshjawane.github.io/posts/aws-account-security/</guid>
      <description>Securing AWS Env  Deploying an infra, is almost pretty straight forward now a days. There are multiple tools which helps you to automate the things and manage it in better way and update regularly. But talking about the data transport, many people take about the account and data security. If you re setting up an infra on AWS, you might be interested in implement following things to make you AWS infra more secure</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
